<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ethereum on Shinra</title>
    <link>https://shinra-corp.com/tags/ethereum/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ethereum on Shinra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:46:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shinra-corp.com/tags/ethereum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Interest Fund</title>
      <link>https://shinra-corp.com/project/interest-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shinra-corp.com/project/interest-fund/</guid>
      <description>Interest Fund Fund a Project with DAI Compound Interest. You don&amp;rsquo;t give away your money only the interest of that deposit. You can think that you are giving your time. A donor can start funding one project then change to another project at any time.
You can start your week giving your interest to help some project you use, than withdraw and start funding a human rights project and by the weekend you give to DLX Meetup so we can create more fun examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MultiSign Wallet</title>
      <link>https://shinra-corp.com/project/multisign-wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shinra-corp.com/project/multisign-wallet/</guid>
      <description> MultiSignature Wallet Controling our world domination plans with multi private keys.
With this wallet you can send ether and tokens by signing a off-cahin message! Someone have to submit all signatures to the wallet contract do make the transaction.
This is still a Work in Progress and are missing many tests! Please by aware this is a learning project, don&amp;rsquo;t trust the code, review it! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mako</title>
      <link>https://shinra-corp.com/project/mako/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shinra-corp.com/project/mako/</guid>
      <description>Mako is the energy for modern world! We transform Mako liquid in electricity, so we can live a good modern life! Some people say that exposure to Mako can poison a person, but that&amp;rsquo;s not true, you can get same Mako as new form of free (not free) and cheap (not cheap) energy to the decentralized Corporation that we are!
How can you collect some Mako? The idea is very simple, you use the contract method paymentProxy to bypass your Ethereum payments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>